<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
	<entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>Engineering Overalls</entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>A set of clothing with all the bells and whistles for the tradesman, including a few pockets to store the tools or snacks. Though the inlaid padding helps with the comfort and protection of the wearer, it does hinder movement a little.</entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>
	<entityname.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>Engineering Overalls (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>
	<entitydescription.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>A set of clothing with all the bells and whistles for the tradesman, including a few pockets to store the tools or snacks. Though the inlaid padding helps with the comfort and protection of the wearer, it does hinder movement a little. Maybe blue isn't your color.</entitydescription.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>
	<entityname.sgt_cowboy>Stetson Hat</entityname.sgt_cowboy>
	<entitydescription.sgt_cowboy>A hat made of crawler-leather that just feels plain good to wear, and seals your status as the gunslinger-type.</entitydescription.sgt_cowboy>
	<entityname.sgt_trenchcoat>Trenchcoat</entityname.sgt_trenchcoat>
	<entitydescription.sgt_trenchcoat>An exotic Thresher-leather longcoat that's thick enough to protect from both creature and cold, but light enough to showboat comfortably over your uniform.</entitydescription.sgt_trenchcoat>
	<entityname.sgt_longrangeradio>Radio Range Extender Pack</entityname.sgt_longrangeradio>
	<entitydescription.sgt_longrangeradio>Links up with the user's headset to broadcast at a significantly longer range than normal. Has a few pockets on the sides for spare equipment.</entitydescription.sgt_longrangeradio>
	<entityname.sgt_bobag>Coalition Black-Ops Specialist Hardcase</entityname.sgt_bobag>
	<entitydescription.sgt_bobag>A Hardcase with a built-in range extender for radio equipment. It comes with a few deeper-than-usual pockets for spare munitions, as well as a sling for putting heavy weapons away, and out of sight.</entitydescription.sgt_bobag>
	<entityname.sgt_exogear>Coalition Exoskeleton</entityname.sgt_exogear>
	<entitydescription.sgt_exogear>A semi-experimental suit used predominantly by miners and logistics teams for easy transport of materials and heavy equipment, whilst having a decent degree of ballistic protection. This suit however hampers movement given it's overall weight and the servomotors require a significant amount of power to function under load. Pressure rated for 2km/2000m.</entitydescription.sgt_exogear>
	<entityname.sgt_fieldcap>Coalition Patrol Cap</entityname.sgt_fieldcap>
	<entitydescription.sgt_fieldcap>Regulation wear, when a ballistic helmet is updressing the job, but you still want something on your noggin'.</entitydescription.sgt_fieldcap>
	<entityname.sgt_combatmedicuniform>Combat Medic Uniform (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_combatmedicuniform>
	<entitydescription.sgt_combatmedicuniform>A uniform with a unique looking digital camouflage printed onto it. It features thick aramid padding and larger pockets for equipment. Bloodstains are hard to wash out of clothing.</entitydescription.sgt_combatmedicuniform>
	<entityname.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>Renegade Combat Medic Uniform (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>
	<entitydescription.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>A uniform meant to distinguish the wearer from Coalition medics, however is made with less materials and compromises protection and capacity for greater agility. Bloodstains are hard to wash out of clothing.</entitydescription.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>
	<entityname.sgt_lightuniform>Coalition Combat Fatigues (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_lightuniform>
	<entitydescription.sgt_lightuniform>A 2-piece, professional looking Coalition BDU, providing a comfortable means of identifying oneself. I guess you decided it's time to roll up your sleeves, huh?</entitydescription.sgt_lightuniform>
	<entityname.sgt_renegadeuniform>Renegade Combat Fatigues (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_renegadeuniform>
	<entitydescription.sgt_renegadeuniform>A standard issue Separatist uniform, providing a small amount of protection though allows for slightly more agile movement. I guess just ripping off your sleeves is just too punk, huh?</entitydescription.sgt_renegadeuniform>
	<entityname.sgt_combatrig>Coalition Black-Ops Rig</entityname.sgt_combatrig>
	<entitydescription.sgt_combatrig>An extremely experimental combat suit, designed for the Coalition Black-Ops. A Uniform with advanced alloys and flexible joints, it allows a great deal of protection from gunfire, while keeping the user mobile enough to evade and reposition in the case of overwhelming force.</entitydescription.sgt_combatrig>
	<entityname.sgt_boshotgun>Coalition Suppressed Combat Shotgun</entityname.sgt_boshotgun>
	<entitydescription.sgt_boshotgun>A tactical mag-fed design, suppressed for use by Black-Ops. Using Renegade-style 12 gauge magazines, it substantially increases overall menueverability of the weapon, as well as reduce the required user-effort to cycle, though this method has a chance to jam if the mechanism gets too hot.</entitydescription.sgt_boshotgun>
	<entityname.sgt_bopmr>Coalition Precision Marksman Rifle</entityname.sgt_bopmr>
	<entitydescription.sgt_bopmr>A 8.6x70mm straight-pull rifle, suppressed to the liking of the Black-Ops, using a bullpup frame to allow a longer barrel behind the suppressor, though it still needs to be stowed on the back due to it's sheer akwardness.</entitydescription.sgt_bopmr>
	<entityname.sgt_boarmorhaz>Coalition Black-Ops Hazardous Environment Panels</entityname.sgt_boarmorhaz>
	<entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhaz>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Hazardous Environment Variants were developed for the more chem-savvy individuals, when such is used in the field, and comes with slots for drugs and antidotes.  Rated for 3000m Pressure.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhaz>
	<entityname.sgt_boarmorleg>Coalition Black-Ops Mobility Assist Panels</entityname.sgt_boarmorleg>
	<entitydescription.sgt_boarmorleg>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Mobility Assist Variants are a little clunky, as the straps don't allow other armors to be worn, however they passively boost the users mobility, and keeps them on their feet.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorleg>
	<entityname.sgt_boarmorhvy>Coalition Black-Ops Heavy Engagement Panels</entityname.sgt_boarmorhvy>
	<entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhvy>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Heavy Engagement Variants are made to provide additional frontal armor, and aid in weapons usage at the cost of some flexibility.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhvy>
	<entityname.sgt_boarmorsap>Coalition Black-Ops Explosive Diffusal Components</entityname.sgt_boarmorsap>
	<entitydescription.sgt_boarmorsap>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Explosive Diffusal Variants, also known as "Sapper Components," are sensors wired throughout the rig to sense electromagnetic disruptions and give a view of electrical systems, alongside kevlar wrappings to secure the user against explosives, though these cover some of the color indicators.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorsap>
	<entityname.sgt_blackopshelm>Coalition Black-Ops Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm>
	<entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. While providing great protection from gunfire, it's lightweight structure allows more comfortable movement and weapons use.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm>
	<entityname.sgt_blackopshelm2>Coalition Black-Ops Heavy Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm2>
	<entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm2>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. Using heavier plates, it allows more intensive situations to come out more favorably with less injuries incurred.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm2>
	<entityname.sgt_blackopshelm3>Coalition Black-Ops Hazard Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm3>
	<entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm3>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. With hermetical seals and a line for a gas tank, it keeps the user safe from most hazards without complicating the situation, as it will engage the regulator automatically.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm3>
	<entityname.sgt_blackopshelm4>Coalition Black-Ops Sapper Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm4>
	<entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm4>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. Integrated with a tactical interface to key-in information about devices, it allows the user to interact with components with increased aptitude, though this was at a sacrifice to protection.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm4>
	<entityname.sgt_tachelm>Tactical Combat Helmet</entityname.sgt_tachelm>
	<entitydescription.sgt_tachelm>A Combat Helmet designed with integrated thermal optics, allowing for the wearer to have significantly better capabilities in close quarters. However, due to the bulky nature of the optics, armour plating has been reduced and therefore makes it less protective. The lenses are also sensitive to water and thus automatically turn off when submerged.</entitydescription.sgt_tachelm>
	<entityname.sgt_medhelm>Combat Medic Helmet</entityname.sgt_medhelm>
	<entitydescription.sgt_medhelm>A Combat Helmet with a built in medical scanner, used to quickly evaluate an injured crew member's status whilst providing a notable degree of protection from small arms. The scanner used however is significantly more power hungry than it's standard issue counterpart and therefore requires third party batteries to remain functional.</entitydescription.sgt_medhelm>
	<entityname.scp_bodyrig>Plate Carrier Rig</entityname.scp_bodyrig>
	<entitydescription.scp_bodyrig>A standard issue vest featuring a bandolier for the storage of ammunition.</entitydescription.scp_bodyrig>
	<entityname.scp_heavyvest>Heavy Body Armour</entityname.scp_heavyvest>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavyvest>A modernized version of the current Coalition vests, further designed to protect against rifle projectiles and will likely become Coalition standard issue at some point, despite the increased weight of the plates and aramid soft armour.</entitydescription.scp_heavyvest>
	<entityname.scp_heavyrig>Heavy Carrier Rig</entityname.scp_heavyrig>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavyrig>A futher modified vest meant to further enhance it's capabilities in combat, featuring pouches and armour for the extremities. This does however noticably increase it's weight.</entitydescription.scp_heavyrig>
	<entityname.scp_specialrig>Special Carrier Rig</entityname.scp_specialrig>
	<entitydescription.scp_specialrig>A large, intimidating vest utilizing advanced anti-ballistic materials to provide excellent protection against even AP rifle projectiles. As it's specifically designed for outpost assaulting, it's a poor choice for daily usage.</entitydescription.scp_specialrig>
	<entityname.scp_renegadespecialrig>Renegade Special Carrier Rig</entityname.scp_renegadespecialrig>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadespecialrig>An incredibly bulky looking vest made to be the Separatist's cheaper alternative to the Coalition's Special Rig, however the lack of advanced materials makes the vest incredibly cumbersome.</entitydescription.scp_renegadespecialrig>
	<entityname.scp_simplehelmet>Improvised Combat Helmet</entityname.scp_simplehelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_simplehelmet>A simple steel and rubber helmet that provides basic protection against sharp objects, however provides minimal protection against projectiles given the helmet's quality and materials.</entitydescription.scp_simplehelmet>
	<entityname.scp_combathelmet>Combat Helmet</entityname.scp_combathelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_combathelmet>An upgrade package to the standard issue Coalition headgear for better protection against the ever increasing proliferation of rifles and AP projectiles. it has a ballistic mandible and visor instead of a simple faceshield, worsening field of view.</entitydescription.scp_combathelmet>
	<entityname.scp_heavycombathelmet>Heavy Combat Helmet</entityname.scp_heavycombathelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavycombathelmet>A large and bulky helmet using an anti-ballistic superalloy to protect even against significant AP rifle threats, at the cost of a hefty price tag and weight.</entitydescription.scp_heavycombathelmet>
	<entityname.scp_renegadeheavyhelmet>Renegade Heavy Combat Helmet</entityname.scp_renegadeheavyhelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadeheavyhelmet>A heavier, more producible version of the Coalition's alternative, using simpler materials however needs to have thicker layers of armour to compete against similar threats.</entitydescription.scp_renegadeheavyhelmet>
	<entityname.scp_renegadecaptainhat>Renegade Captain's Hat</entityname.scp_renegadecaptainhat>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadecaptainhat>A basic hat made from aramid fibers and cloth, making it more protective against small arms, though not by much due to the lack of thickness.</entitydescription.scp_renegadecaptainhat>
	<entityname.scp_alienhelmet>Fractal Helmet</entityname.scp_alienhelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_alienhelmet>A large helmet of alien origin which encompasses the entire head and is strangely suited for human anatomy.</entitydescription.scp_alienhelmet>
	<entityname.scp_assaultpack>Assault Backpack</entityname.scp_assaultpack>
	<entitydescription.scp_assaultpack>A conveniently sized backpack designed for general purpose use. Almost anyone can find a use for such a utile pack, from combat medic work, to mining missions and infantry combat.</entitydescription.scp_assaultpack>
	<entityname.scp_heavypack>Collosal Backpack</entityname.scp_heavypack>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavypack>A gigantic backpack that can almost fit another person in, utilized primarily for salvage missions or for very long hauls outside of a submarine. It's inherent weight and bulkiness severely hampers movement, making it a large liability in combat without assistance.</entitydescription.scp_heavypack>
	<entityname.scp_tacpack>Tactical Backpack</entityname.scp_tacpack>
	<entitydescription.scp_tacpack>A more spacious backpack designed to fit more equipment or materials in, however is heavier as a result.</entitydescription.scp_tacpack>
	<entityname.scp_protopack>Prototype Backpack</entityname.scp_protopack>
	<entitydescription.scp_protopack>A top of the line, low profile backpack using a heavy duty Durasteel frame and large weapon mount, making carrying a heavy weapon around significantly easier.</entitydescription.scp_protopack>
	<entityname.scp_fieldpack>Field Backpack</entityname.scp_fieldpack>
	<entitydescription.scp_fieldpack>An even larger and heavier backpack meant to carry as much equipment as possible without severely hampering the wearer's capabilities, especially useful for long hauls or mining trips or ammo bearing.</entitydescription.scp_fieldpack>
	<entityname.scp_renegadevest>Renegade Soft Armour</entityname.scp_renegadevest>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadevest>A soft armour vest designed to provide basic protection against low velocity small arms whilst being easy for an insurgent to craft on the submarine.It has small pockets which allow for storage of small items.</entitydescription.scp_renegadevest>
	<entityname.scp_heavyuniform>Coalition Fragmentation Suit</entityname.scp_heavyuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavyuniform>A low profile suit designed for CQC operations where explosives are a factor. It provides protection against fragmentation though provides marginal ballistic protection against firearms, alongside having some weight to it.</entitydescription.scp_heavyuniform>
	<entityname.scp_heavyrenuniform>Renegade Fragmentation Suit</entityname.scp_heavyrenuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavyrenuniform>A bulkier alternative to the Coalition's frag suit. Featuring mostly thin steel armour inserts, it's heavier and more awkward to move in but will regardless protect the user.</entitydescription.scp_heavyrenuniform>
	<entityname.scp_renegadeplatecarrier>Renegade Body Armour</entityname.scp_renegadeplatecarrier>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadeplatecarrier>An armour vest using steel plates to provide protection against small arms fire, whilst significantly more protective than the lighter, soft armour variant it does mean it's heavier than the Coalition alternative.</entitydescription.scp_renegadeplatecarrier>
	<entityname.scp_heavyhazmatuniform>Heavy HAZMAT Suit</entityname.scp_heavyhazmatuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavyhazmatuniform>A HAZMAT Suit which has been modified to further increase it's radiation protection, predominantly against high energy emissions. This however increases the weight of the suit.</entitydescription.scp_heavyhazmatuniform>
	<entityname.scp_liquidatorsuit>Liquidator Suit</entityname.scp_liquidatorsuit>
	<entitydescription.scp_liquidatorsuit>An experimental closed system suit predominantly made of experimental Lead-Dementonite radiation shielding, able to protect against emissions from almost any radiological hazard. It's also capable of protecting from pressure up to 4500m down, a very handy feature for sub reactor meltdowns and emergency pressure protection.</entitydescription.scp_liquidatorsuit>
	<entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuit>Engineering Suit</entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuit>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuit>A set of overalls which have been designed to further protect against cuts and crushes caused by operating and maintaining mechanical devices.</entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuit>
	<entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuitbluesuit2>Engineering Suit</entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuitbluesuit2>
	<entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuitbluesuit2>A set of overalls which have been designed to further protect against cuts and crushes caused by operating and maintaining mechanical devices.</entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuitbluesuit2>
	<entityname.scp_combatmedicuniform>Combat Medic Uniform</entityname.scp_combatmedicuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_combatmedicuniform>A uniform with a unique looking digital camouflage printed onto it. It features thick aramid padding and larger pockets for equipment.</entitydescription.scp_combatmedicuniform>
	<entityname.scp_renegadecombatmedicuniform>Renegade Combat Medic Uniform</entityname.scp_renegadecombatmedicuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadecombatmedicuniform>A uniform meant to distinguish the wearer from Coalition medics, however is made with less materials and compromises protection and capacity for greater agility.</entitydescription.scp_renegadecombatmedicuniform>
	<entityname.scp_renegadeuniform>Renegade Combat Fatigues</entityname.scp_renegadeuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadeuniform>A standard issue Separatist uniform, providing a small amount of protection though allows for slightly more agile movement.</entitydescription.scp_renegadeuniform>
	<entityname.scp_renegadehelmet>Renegade Helmet</entityname.scp_renegadehelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadehelmet>A somewhat easily producible helmet used by the Jovian Separatists providing protection against most threats, though due to the basic materials does faulter slightly against most Coalition helmets.</entitydescription.scp_renegadehelmet>
	<entityname.scp_renegadedivingsuit>Renegade Diving Suit</entityname.scp_renegadedivingsuit>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadedivingsuit>A diving suit utilised by Jovian Separatists to show which faction they are a part of, it has been designed to protect mostly against small arms fire. Has a depth rating of 6,000m.</entitydescription.scp_renegadedivingsuit>
	<entityname.scp_renegadecaptainuniform>Renegade Captain Uniform</entityname.scp_renegadecaptainuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_renegadecaptainuniform>A uniform worn by Jovian Separatist captains featuring aramid layers to provide negligible protection against small arms.</entitydescription.scp_renegadecaptainuniform>
	<entityname.scp_combathardsuit>Combat Hardsuit</entityname.scp_combathardsuit>
	<entitydescription.scp_combathardsuit>A heavy duty Diving Suit used for providing vastly more protection against small arms and creatures than any other option. However this suit severely hampers tool usage in addition having to having poorer oxygen cycling efficiency. It's servomotors are also incredibly power hungry and rapidly drain battery cells.</entitydescription.scp_combathardsuit>
	<entityname.scp_softvest>Soft Armour Vest</entityname.scp_softvest>
	<entitydescription.scp_softvest>A lightweight and low profile vest made of aramid fibres, making it more comfortable to wear but is much less effective against high velocity projectiles. A specialised shoulder pad allows for more comfortable shouldering of firearms.</entitydescription.scp_softvest>
	<entityname.scp_riotvest>Riot Vest</entityname.scp_riotvest>
	<entitydescription.scp_riotvest>A basic vest with internal and external padding for protecting against bladed and blunt attacks, though fairs extremely poorly against small arms fire.</entitydescription.scp_riotvest>
	<entityname.scp_bulldozerhelm>Dozer Helmet</entityname.scp_bulldozerhelm>
	<entitydescription.scp_bulldozerhelm>An extremely heavy and bulky helmet with a large plate in front, providing near inpenetrable protection against small arms fire. As a result of the front plate's small eyeholes it dramatically reduces the wearer's field of vision and ability to equip items.</entitydescription.scp_bulldozerhelm>
	<entityname.scp_yuihelmet>Infiltrator Helmet</entityname.scp_yuihelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_yuihelmet>A low profile helmet composed of Prototype composite materials, making it a light yet protective helmet, the visor housing an augmented reality headset for significantly increasing the wearer's combat capabilities.</entitydescription.scp_yuihelmet>
	<entityname.scp_livhelmet>Vanguard Helmet</entityname.scp_livhelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_livhelmet>A heavy duty Phyisicorium helmet housing an experimental augmented reality headset, for significantly increasing the wearer's combat capabilities.</entitydescription.scp_livhelmet>
	<entityname.scp_yuirig>Infiltrator Vest</entityname.scp_yuirig>
	<entitydescription.scp_yuirig>A low profile vest that uses intricate Durasteel-Titanium Dragon Skin plating, making it respectively protective whilst staying incredibly light.</entitydescription.scp_yuirig>
	<entityname.scp_livrig>Vanguard Rig</entityname.scp_livrig>
	<entitydescription.scp_livrig>A heavily customized and maintained rig with Physicorium-Polymer plates on the front, back and sides for maximum protection.</entitydescription.scp_livrig>
	<entityname.scp_specopsuniform>Infiltrator Fragmentation Suit</entityname.scp_specopsuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_specopsuniform>A Renegade Frag Suit that has had a significant overhaul by the previous user, using highly sophisticated soft armour and flexible materials around the areas of the body that require the least protection.</entitydescription.scp_specopsuniform>
	<entityname.scp_livuniform>Vanguard Ballistic Undersuit</entityname.scp_livuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_livuniform>An advanced undersuit utilizing an experimental Durasteel-Silicon Carbide plating for excellent protection against both fragmentation and small arms fire.</entitydescription.scp_livuniform>
	<entityname.scp_marauderuniform>Marauder Undersuit</entityname.scp_marauderuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_marauderuniform>A very heavily modified Combat Medic Uniform that's been turned into a combat undersuit, utilizing rifle rated armour and thicker aramid layers. </entitydescription.scp_marauderuniform>
	<entityname.scp_veronuniform>Protectorate Fragmentation Suit</entityname.scp_veronuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_veronuniform>A very heavily customised Fragmentation Suit designed to protect against non-AP rifle threats whilst significantly enhancing anti-explosive properties. </entitydescription.scp_veronuniform>
	<entityname.scp_marauderrig>Marauder Rig</entityname.scp_marauderrig>
	<entitydescription.scp_marauderrig>A top of the line, low profile vest using Durasteel-Physicorium plates, designed to minimize bulk and maximize protection. </entitydescription.scp_marauderrig>
	<entityname.scp_marauderhelmet>Marauder Helmet</entityname.scp_marauderhelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_marauderhelmet>A top of the line, low profile helmet using the same materials it's counterpart vest uses, allowing for a lightweight and highly protective helmet. </entitydescription.scp_marauderhelmet>
	<entityname.scp_veronrig>Protectorate Rig</entityname.scp_veronrig>
	<entitydescription.scp_veronrig>A pristine and hefty looking plate carrier with protection and storage in mind, made for taking heavy hits whilst having plenty of ammunition to stay in the fight. </entitydescription.scp_veronrig>
	<entityname.scp_veronhelmet>Protectorate Helmet</entityname.scp_veronhelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_veronhelmet>A large helmet that encompasses the entire head in rifle rated armour, using Durasteel alloys to significantly reduce weight. </entitydescription.scp_veronhelmet>
	<entityname.scp_ae035>Strange Mask</entityname.scp_ae035>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035>A mildly disturbing and uncanny looking mask, with a substance similar to Preso-Latex constantly secreting from both the eye and mouth parts with no apparent mechanism to do so. Who made it, why, how and when is a mystery, though researchers in outposts will definitely want their hands on such a mysterious artefact.</entitydescription.scp_ae035>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Tragic Mask</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>???</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Calamity</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Insanity</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Despair</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Sadism</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Iblis</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Satan</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>Armageddon</entityname.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>YOUARENOTWELCOMEHERE</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>ISMILEUPONYOURMISFORTUNE</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>HELLAWAITSYOU</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>TRAGEDYWILLARRIVE</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>YOURFINALDESTINATIONISNOTHERE</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>BREAKTHECYCLE</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>JOVESEESALL</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>OURFATHERTHOUARTINHELLDAMNATIONBETHYNAME.</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>01010011010000110101000000101101001100000011001100110101.</entitydescription.scp_ae035tragedy>
	<entityname.scp_lightuniform>Coalition Combat Fatigues</entityname.scp_lightuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_lightuniform>A 2-piece, professional looking Coalition BDU, providing a comfortable means of identifying oneself.</entitydescription.scp_lightuniform>
	<entityname.scp_hazmathelmet>HAZMAT Headpiece</entityname.scp_hazmathelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_hazmathelmet>A lead lined hood made of a hydrophobic synthetic fabric meant to be either draped over or tucked into a uniform. It features a hardened diving mask with thicker rubber parts to better protect against more penetrating radiation.</entitydescription.scp_hazmathelmet>
	<entityname.scp_cbrnsuit>CBRN Suit</entityname.scp_cbrnsuit>
	<entitydescription.scp_cbrnsuit>A 1-piece hydrophobic suit and helmet designed for protection against radiological and chemical threats with some degree of anti-ballistic ability.</entitydescription.scp_cbrnsuit>
	<entityname.scp_cbrnhelmet>CBRN Helmet</entityname.scp_cbrnhelmet>
	<entitydescription.scp_cbrnhelmet>A combat helmet fitted with a HAZMAT hood and Hardened Diving Mask, the hood predomintantly using soft armour.</entitydescription.scp_cbrnhelmet>
	<entityname.scp_hardeneddivingmask>Hardened Diving Mask</entityname.scp_hardeneddivingmask>
	<entitydescription.scp_hardeneddivingmask>A heavy duty diving mask with steel inserts, thick rubber and plexiglass lenses for better protection against facial injuries.</entitydescription.scp_hardeneddivingmask>
	<entityname.scp_clownbatuniform>Honkbat Ensemble</entityname.scp_clownbatuniform>
	<entitydescription.scp_clownbatuniform>A clown outfit made for protecting the Honkmother's servants.</entitydescription.scp_clownbatuniform>
	<entityname.scp_clownbatmask>Honkbat Ballistic Mask</entityname.scp_clownbatmask>
	<entitydescription.scp_clownbatmask>A full-face Ballistic mask for both protecting against lower velocity projectiles whilst preserving your beliefs.</entitydescription.scp_clownbatmask>
	<entityname.scp_interceptorsuit>Interceptor Diving Suit</entityname.scp_interceptorsuit>
	<entitydescription.scp_interceptorsuit>An experimental combat suit built upon an existing Slipsuit, using shark biomimicry to minimize water resistance for significantly better water travel. It also features Durasteel armour plating to make it more effective against small arms.</entitydescription.scp_interceptorsuit>
	
	<!-- CA items -->
	<entityname.feniterhazmats>Advanced Hazmat Suit</entityname.feniterhazmats>
	<entitydescription.feniterhazmats>Modified military hazardous materials suit. Suit power enables lights and assisted closed circuit breathing apparatus with battery in suit. Suit's internal gel protects from sudden water flow and may act as a diving suit in a pinch with slow movement. Multi-functional goggles that allow thermal, low light vision, and health-scanner function.</entitydescription.feniterhazmats>
	<entityname.fenitercbrneod>Heavy EOD Suit</entityname.fenitercbrneod>
	<entitydescription.fenitercbrneod>Heavy duty combined EOD/CBRN suit. Boasts imperviousness to almost all chemical hazards and extremely heavy resistance against most explosive, incendiary and physical hazards.</entitydescription.fenitercbrneod>
</infotexts>