<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <Override>
    <entityname.smg>Surplus Submachine Gun</entityname.smg>
    <entitydescription.smg>An old and used 11.43x23mm SMG, it's design having been on Europa since humanity arrived. Its large sealed bolt severely hampers its cyclic rate and as a result it has been mostly phased out by other options, as more sophisticated bolt designs were made allowing for more reliable options to be developed.</entitydescription.smg>
    <entityname.smgmagazine>Surplus SMG Magazine</entityname.smgmagazine>
    <entitydescription.smgmagazine>An old 25 round 11.43x23mm magazine meant for use in the older Coalition SMGs, its shape designed for the cartridges that contain an older form of oxidizing propellant.</entitydescription.smgmagazine>
    <entityname.smgmagazinedepletedfuel>Surplus SMG DU Magazine</entityname.smgmagazinedepletedfuel>
    <entitydescription.smgmagazinedepletedfuel>An old 25 round 11.43x23mm magazine loaded with custom Depleted Uranium projectiles for better effectiveness against armour, though has awful terminal ballistics.</entitydescription.smgmagazinedepletedfuel>
    <entityname.smground></entityname.smground>
    <entitydescription.smground></entitydescription.smground>
    <entityname.revolver>Surplus Revolver</entityname.revolver>
    <entitydescription.revolver>A 9x29mm revolver using an antiquated cartridge. It has a very light double action trigger mechanism.</entitydescription.revolver>
    <entityname.revolverround>Surplus Revolver Round</entityname.revolverround>
    <entitydescription.revolverround>An old 9x29mm cartridge that appears to no longer be produced on Europa anymore. Despite this, it is incredibly common due to the collosal Surplus, however has sub-par capabilities compared to modern options.</entitydescription.revolverround>
    <entityname.revolverrounddepletedfuel>Surplus Revolver Round</entityname.revolverrounddepletedfuel>
    <entitydescription.revolverrounddepletedfuel>An old 9x29mm cartridge, custom made to have a special DU projectile for better performance against armour, sacrificing a lot of terminal ballistics.</entitydescription.revolverrounddepletedfuel>
    <entityname.shotgun>Surplus Pump Action Shotgun</entityname.shotgun>
    <entitydescription.shotgun>A very worn and cheap 12 Gauge shotgun with a very stiff pump action, originally designed for unarmoured targets and general security. It has been entirely phased out by contemporary options.</entitydescription.shotgun>
    <entityname.shotgunshell>12 Gauge Shotgun Buckshot Shell</entityname.shotgunshell>
    <entitydescription.shotgunshell>An 12 Gauge shotgun shell containing buckshot. Being found all across Europa, it is renowned for it's close quarters lethality despite it's non-existent armour penetration.</entitydescription.shotgunshell>
    <entityname.ancientweapon>Fractal Deconstruction Device</entityname.ancientweapon>
    <entitydescription.ancientweapon>A strange, organic looking device made out of various heavy metals and Fulgurium, cutting materials via concentrated gamma irradiation.</entitydescription.ancientweapon>
    <entityname.harpoongun>Harpoon Launcher</entityname.harpoongun>
    <entitydescription.harpoongun>A basic weapon meant for taking on common Europan denizens, however is a terrible choice for force on force combat.</entitydescription.harpoongun>
    <entityname.smgunique>Aftermarket Surplus SMG</entityname.smgunique>
    <entitydescription.smgunique>A surplus SMG modified by the previous user, featuring a longer barrel, burst trigger group, larger gas block and an optic. This was evidently customized for longer distance engagements.</entitydescription.smgunique>
    <entityname.shotgununique>Veteran's Double Barrel Shotgun</entityname.shotgununique>
    <entitydescription.shotgununique>A very old shotgun with 2 side-by-side barrels and linked triggers, allowing for 2 shells to be discharged almost immediately. Unfortunately due to being a double barreled shotgun its capacity is inferior to practically every other design.</entitydescription.shotgununique>
    <entityname.handcannon>Veteran's Hand Cannon</entityname.handcannon>
    <entitydescription.handcannon>A massive 15.5x50mm revolver that uses a ridiculously large cartridge, resembling a small grenade shell. It has a very heavy double action trigger mechanism.</entitydescription.handcannon>
    <entityname.handcannonround>Veteran's Hand Cannon Round</entityname.handcannonround>
    <entitydescription.handcannonround>A massive 15.5x50mm cartridge with a Titanium-Alloy jacketed Physicorium core, capable of penetrating multiple enemies causing massive damage.</entitydescription.handcannonround>
    <entityname.assaultrifle>Surplus Assault Rifle</entityname.assaultrifle>
    <entitydescription.assaultrifle>A 6.8x51mm assault rifle that was one of the first of it's kind on Europa, using a powerful and experimental cartridge for punching through mudraptor shells, however it has been discontinued given it's slow fire rate and weight.</entitydescription.assaultrifle>
    <entityname.assaultriflemagazine>Surplus Assault Rifle Magazine</entityname.assaultriflemagazine>
    <entitydescription.assaultriflemagazine>A steel 20 round 6.8x51mm magazine containing old experimental ammunition, composed of a steel jacket with a Physicorium core. This ammo has however been discontinued given it's cost.</entitydescription.assaultriflemagazine>
    <entityname.assaultrifleround>assaultrifleround</entityname.assaultrifleround>
    <entitydescription.assaultrifleround></entitydescription.assaultrifleround>
    <entityname.autoshotgun>Surplus Combat Shotgun</entityname.autoshotgun>
    <entitydescription.autoshotgun>A very early 12 Gauge shotgun design, meant to be significantly more viable against the large crawler populations that were first encountered, it's incredibly heavy thanks to be bolt carrier and internal magazine.</entitydescription.autoshotgun>
    <entityname.stungundart>Stun Gun Dart</entityname.stungundart>
    <entitydescription.stungundart>A small electronic dart designed to inflict multiple short burst electric currents over a period of time into the person it sticks into, causing involuntary muscle movement and temporary paralysis.</entitydescription.stungundart>
    <entityname.spear>Harpoon</entityname.spear>
    <entitydescription.spear>A simple rod of steel with a sharp, barbed point on the end for use against fish and your own crew.</entitydescription.spear>
    <entityname.magnesium>Magnesium</entityname.magnesium>
    <entitydescription.magnesium>An alkali metal that is popular as a propellant on Europa for various low calibre cartridges and some medicines.</entitydescription.magnesium>
    <entityname.flashpowder>Flash Powder</entityname.flashpowder>
    <entitydescription.flashpowder>A mixture of metallic fuel and oxidizer, it is extensively used in large calibre ammunition for providing adequate velocities.</entitydescription.flashpowder>
    <entityname.lead>Lead</entityname.lead>
    <entitydescription.lead>A heavy metal that is easy to melt and cast with. This material is in extremely high demand due to it's use in ammunition and radiation shielding.</entitydescription.lead>
    <entityname.grenadelauncher>Surplus Grenade Launcher</entityname.grenadelauncher>
    <entitydescription.grenadelauncher>A worn and old 40x46mm grenade launcher used for area denial or attacking multiple targets within a group, evidently it's pretty lackluster compared to other options.</entitydescription.grenadelauncher>
    <entityname.stungrenade>Stun Grenade</entityname.stungrenade>
    <entitydescription.stungrenade>A less-than-lethal grenade meant to disorient aggressive individuals without causing significant harm, creating an intense bang and blinding light. It has a 1.5 second fuze.</entitydescription.stungrenade>
    <entityname.shotgunshellblunt>12 Gauge Rubber Shotgun Slug</entityname.shotgunshellblunt>
    <entitydescription.shotgunshellblunt>A 12 gauge slug made completely out of rubber, made for pain compliance and subduing troublemakers without needing other options. However due to its less-lethal nature it is a terrible choice for a person who is armed and an immediate threat to others.</entitydescription.shotgunshellblunt>
    <entityname.hmg>Surplus HMG</entityname.hmg>
    <entitydescription.hmg>A hefty 8.6x70mm Machine Gun meant for powerful sustained fire, though it's primitive recoil system paired with the cartridge makes it extremely hard to control.</entitydescription.hmg>
    <entityname.hmgmagazine>Surplus HMG Magazine</entityname.hmgmagazine>
    <entitydescription.hmgmagazine>A large 100 round 8.6x70mm Machine Gun magazine.</entitydescription.hmgmagazine>
    <entityname.rifle>Surplus Rifle</entityname.rifle>
    <entitydescription.rifle>An old 7.62x67mm Bolt Action Rifle with a 40mm UGL that used as a precursor to both battle and marksman rifles. It is quite often used despite it's obsolesence.</entitydescription.rifle>
    <entityname.riflebullet>Surplus Rifle Cartridge</entityname.riflebullet>
    <entitydescription.riflebullet>A 7.62x67mm FMJ cartridge, being one of the first successful prototype supercavitating options on Europa, making it ideal for long distance fauna hunting.</entitydescription.riflebullet>
    <entityname.machinepistol>Surplus Machine Pistol</entityname.machinepistol>
    <entitydescription.machinepistol>An 11.43x23mm firearm made to bridge the gap between the Revolver and SMG, however is unpopular due to it's recoil, inaccuracy and lackluster power.</entitydescription.machinepistol>
    <entityname.fraggrenade>Fragmentation Grenade</entityname.fraggrenade>
    <entitydescription.fraggrenade>A standard issue hand grenade with a thin steel casing meant to break apart on detonation, it has a 5m explosion radius and 9m fragmentation radius.</entitydescription.fraggrenade>
    <entityname.backpack>Utility Backpack</entityname.backpack>
    <entitydescription.backpack>A custom backpack design meant to be both spacious and low profile, mainly designed for use by engineers and medics.</entitydescription.backpack>
    <entityname.bodyarmor>Coalition Plate Carrier</entityname.bodyarmor>
    <entitydescription.bodyarmor>A standard issue hard armour vest for Coalition forces, it is found almost everywhere given the proliferation of rifles.</entitydescription.bodyarmor>
    <entityname.ballistichelmet1>Coalition Ballistic Helmet</entityname.ballistichelmet1>
    <entitydescription.ballistichelmet1>A standard issue helmet with a visor, focussed on providing ballistic protection, it is able to shrug off pistol shots and some rifle cartridges though is awful for blunt hits.</entitydescription.ballistichelmet1>
    <entityname.ballistichelmet2>Crew Helmet</entityname.ballistichelmet2>
    <entitydescription.ballistichelmet2>A soft armour helmet made for submarine gunners, being significantly less obtrusive when manning periscopes whilst retaining some form of protection.</entitydescription.ballistichelmet2>
    <entityname.ballistichelmet3>Riot Helmet</entityname.ballistichelmet3>
    <entitydescription.ballistichelmet3>A solid helmet with a visor, made for withstanding bladed and blunt impacts and is an excellent choice for melee combat, though is incapable of protecting against bullets.</entitydescription.ballistichelmet3>
  </Override>
</infotexts>