<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <entityname.sgt_locker>Weapons Locker</entityname.sgt_locker>
  <entitydescription.sgt_locker>A Card-Protected Lockaway that only your crew can access. Useful for open-access weapons, as unrecognised personel cannot use its contents.</entitydescription.sgt_locker>
  <entityname.sgt_timedet>Timed Explosive Detonator</entityname.sgt_timedet>
  <entitydescription.sgt_timedet>A plantable timed detonator for explosive bricks, starts at 60s, but can go as low as 10s. Destroys itself after use.</entitydescription.sgt_timedet>
  <entityname.sgt_cowboy>Stetson Hat</entityname.sgt_cowboy>
  <entitydescription.sgt_cowboy>A hat made of crawler-leather that just feels plain good to wear, and seals your status as the gunslinger-type.</entitydescription.sgt_cowboy>
  <entityname.sgt_trenchcoat>Trenchcoat</entityname.sgt_trenchcoat>
  <entitydescription.sgt_trenchcoat>An exotic Thresher-leather longcoat that's thick enough to protect from both creature and cold, but light enough to showboat comfortably over your uniform.</entitydescription.sgt_trenchcoat>
  <entityname.sgt_longrangeradio>Radio Range Extender Pack</entityname.sgt_longrangeradio>
  <entitydescription.sgt_longrangeradio>Links up with the user's headset to broadcast at a significantly longer range than normal. Has a few pockets on the sides for spare equipment.</entitydescription.sgt_longrangeradio>
  <entityname.sgt_bobag>Coalition Black-Ops Specialist Hardcase</entityname.sgt_bobag>
  <entitydescription.sgt_bobag>A Hardcase with a built-in range extender for radio equipment. It comes with a few deeper-than-usual pockets for spare munitions, as well as a sling for putting heavy weapons away, and out of sight.</entitydescription.sgt_bobag>
  <entityname.sgt_exogear>Utility Exoskeleton</entityname.sgt_exogear>
  <entitydescription.sgt_exogear>A semi-experimental suit used predominantly by miners and logistics teams for easy transport of materials and heavy equipment, whilst having a decent degree of ballistic protection. This suit however hampers movement given it's overall weight and the servomotors require a significant amount of power to function under load. Pressure rated for 2km/2000m.</entitydescription.sgt_exogear>
  <entityname.sgt_fieldcap>Patrol Cap</entityname.sgt_fieldcap>
  <entitydescription.sgt_fieldcap>Regulation wear, when a ballistic helmet is updressing the job, but you still want something on your noggin'.</entitydescription.sgt_fieldcap>
  <entityname.sgt_combatmedicuniform>Combat Medic Uniform (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_combatmedicuniform>
  <entitydescription.sgt_combatmedicuniform>A uniform with a unique looking digital camouflage printed onto it. It features thick aramid padding and larger pockets for equipment. Bloodstains are hard to wash out of clothing.</entitydescription.sgt_combatmedicuniform>
  <entityname.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>Renegade Combat Medic Uniform (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>
  <entitydescription.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>A uniform meant to distinguish the wearer from Coalition medics, however is made with less materials and compromises protection and capacity for greater agility. Bloodstains are hard to wash out of clothing.</entitydescription.sgt_renegadecombatmedicuniform>
  <entityname.sgt_lightuniform>Coalition Combat Fatigues (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_lightuniform>
  <entitydescription.sgt_lightuniform>A 2-piece, professional looking Coalition BDU, providing a comfortable means of identifying oneself. I guess you decided it's time to roll up your sleeves, huh?</entitydescription.sgt_lightuniform>
  <entityname.sgt_renegadeuniform>Renegade Combat Fatigues (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_renegadeuniform>
  <entitydescription.sgt_renegadeuniform>A standard issue Separatist uniform, providing a small amount of protection though allows for slightly more agile movement. I guess just ripping off your sleeves is just too punk, huh?</entitydescription.sgt_renegadeuniform>
  <entityname.sgt_combatrig>Coalition Black-Ops Rig</entityname.sgt_combatrig>
  <entitydescription.sgt_combatrig>An extremely experimental combat suit, designed for the Coalition Black-Ops. A Uniform with advanced alloys and flexible joints, it allows a great deal of protection from gunfire, while keeping the user mobile enough to evade and reposition in the case of overwhelming force.</entitydescription.sgt_combatrig>
  <entityname.sgt_boshotgun>Coalition Suppressed Combat Shotgun</entityname.sgt_boshotgun>
  <entitydescription.sgt_boshotgun>A tactical mag-fed design, suppressed for use by Black-Ops. Using Renegade-style 12 gauge magazines, it substantially increases overall menueverability of the weapon, as well as reduce the required user-effort to cycle, though this method has a chance to jam if the mechanism gets too hot.</entitydescription.sgt_boshotgun>
  <entityname.sgt_bopmr>Coalition Precision Marksman Rifle</entityname.sgt_bopmr>
  <entitydescription.sgt_bopmr>A 8.6x70mm straight-pull rifle, suppressed to the liking of the Black-Ops, using a bullpup frame to allow a longer barrel behind the suppressor, though it still needs to be stowed on the back due to it's sheer akwardness.</entitydescription.sgt_bopmr>
  <entityname.sgt_boarmorhaz>Coalition Black-Ops Hazardous Environment Panels</entityname.sgt_boarmorhaz>
  <entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhaz>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Hazardous Environment Variants were developed for the more chem-savvy individuals, when such is used in the field, and comes with slots for drugs and antidotes.  Rated for 3000m Pressure.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhaz>
  <entityname.sgt_boarmorleg>Coalition Black-Ops Mobility Assist Panels</entityname.sgt_boarmorleg>
  <entitydescription.sgt_boarmorleg>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Mobility Assist Variants are a little clunky, as the straps don't allow other armors to be worn, however they passively boost the users mobility, and keeps them on their feet.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorleg>
  <entityname.sgt_boarmorhvy>Coalition Black-Ops Heavy Engagement Panels</entityname.sgt_boarmorhvy>
  <entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhvy>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Heavy Engagement Variants are made to provide additional frontal armor, and aid in weapons usage at the cost of some flexibility.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorhvy>
  <entityname.sgt_boarmorsap>Coalition Black-Ops Explosive Diffusal Components</entityname.sgt_boarmorsap>
  <entitydescription.sgt_boarmorsap>A set of additive plates that attach to the existing system for the Black-Ops Rig. The Explosive Diffusal Variants, also known as "Sapper Components," are sensors wired throughout the rig to sense electromagnetic disruptions and give a view of electrical systems, alongside kevlar wrappings to secure the user against explosives, though these cover some of the color indicators.</entitydescription.sgt_boarmorsap>
  <entityname.sgt_blackopshelm>Coalition Black-Ops Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm>
  <entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. While providing great protection from gunfire, it's lightweight structure allows more comfortable movement and weapons use.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm>
  <entityname.sgt_blackopshelm2>Coalition Black-Ops Heavy Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm2>
  <entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm2>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. Using heavier plates, it allows more intensive situations to come out more favorably with less injuries incurred.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm2>
  <entityname.sgt_blackopshelm3>Coalition Black-Ops Hazard Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm3>
  <entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm3>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. With hermetical seals and a line for a gas tank, it keeps the user safe from most hazards without complicating the situation, as it will engage the regulator automatically.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm3>
  <entityname.sgt_blackopshelm4>Coalition Black-Ops Sapper Helmet</entityname.sgt_blackopshelm4>
  <entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm4>An optimised helmet giving full view of the combat sector, suited for Coalition Black-Ops. Integrated with a tactical interface to key-in information about devices, it allows the user to interact with components with increased aptitude, though this was at a sacrifice to protection.</entitydescription.sgt_blackopshelm4>
  <entityname.sgt_tachelm>Tactical Combat Helmet</entityname.sgt_tachelm>
  <entitydescription.sgt_tachelm>A Combat Helmet designed with integrated thermal optics, allowing for the wearer to have significantly better capabilities in close quarters. However, due to the bulky nature of the optics, armour plating has been reduced and therefore makes it less protective. The lenses are also sensitive to water and thus automatically turn off when submerged.</entitydescription.sgt_tachelm>
  <entityname.sgt_medhelm>Combat Medic Helmet</entityname.sgt_medhelm>
  <entitydescription.sgt_medhelm>A Combat Helmet with a built in medical scanner, used to quickly evaluate an injured crew member's status whilst providing a notable degree of protection from small arms. The scanner used however is significantly more power hungry than it's standard issue counterpart and therefore requires third party batteries to remain functional.</entitydescription.sgt_medhelm>
  <entityname.sgt_boknife>Durasteel-Incendium Alloy Knife</entityname.sgt_boknife>
  <entitydescription.sgt_boknife>A durasteel tactical blade with an Incendium edge, slashing causes an extreme temperature change on contact, often gashing through materials with little resistance.</entitydescription.sgt_boknife>
  <entityname.sgt_f2k>Coalition Suppressed Assault Rifle</entityname.sgt_f2k>
  <entitydescription.sgt_f2k>A highly unusual looking suppressed 5.56x45mm rifle featuring an unconventional ejection system and somewhat alien shape, alongside having a full rifle length barrel in a more compact package. Produced for Black Ops who require a covert weapon that uses more available ammunition.</entitydescription.sgt_f2k>
  <entityname.sgt_xms>Coalition Covert Combat Rifle</entityname.sgt_xms>
  <entitydescription.sgt_xms>An odd rifle loading the natively subsonic 9x39, it squeezes every bit of extra energy for the round, giving it more power and armor piercing. It's cyclical rate is somewhat low, designed to keep it little more than a hoarse whisper, to the preference of Black-Ops Operatives.</entitydescription.sgt_xms>
  <entityname.sgt_vhs>Coalition Suppressed Battle Rifle</entityname.sgt_vhs>
  <entitydescription.sgt_vhs>Loading 7.62x51, Coalition Black-Ops teams needed something with more "Knockdown Potential," in a more compact package. The bullpup design was used to keep the weapon relatively small and light, alongside integral suppressors to mask their presence when deep in enemy territory. The weapon uses a quick 4-round burst firemode to help with overall accuracy, and reduce ammunition waste.</entitydescription.sgt_vhs>
  <entityname.sgt_m90t>Pump-Action Assault Shotgun</entityname.sgt_m90t>
  <entitydescription.sgt_m90t>Designed for multi-role, the Assault Shotgun has a long and complicated service history. Sporting the 8-Gauge shell, it has a nasty habit of breaking faces, doors, and the occasional shoulder, as it's recoil is unforgiving, though there are some who take no less for traitors.</entitydescription.sgt_m90t>
  <entityname.sgt_dbs>Double-Barrel Assault Shotgun</entityname.sgt_dbs>
  <entitydescription.sgt_dbs>A retooled Double-Barrel shotgun, favored by Veterans of any side for it's reliability and commanding feel. With the ability to quickly drop both 8-Gauge shells in a moments notice, it often gets used in a defensive manner, as exchanging shells takes a while-too-long for gunfights.</entitydescription.sgt_dbs>
  <entityname.sgt_gunslinger>Single-Action Light Hand Cannon</entityname.sgt_gunslinger>
  <entitydescription.sgt_gunslinger>A 10.9x33mmR Single-Action revolver, great choice for self-defense, due to it's light trigger pull, but requires the hammer to be drawn back for every subsequent shot. However, the simplicity allows for single-handed use, and more skilled individuals can re-balance it in their hands faster, allowing for quicker shots.</entitydescription.sgt_gunslinger>
  <entityname.sgt_levergun>Service Repeater</entityname.sgt_levergun>
  <entitydescription.sgt_levergun>A 9x29mm rifle utilizing a very old lever action system that is heavily outdated compared to most firearms on Europa. Despite the inherent antiquity, it is favoured by Coalition captains and citizens for making a rather puny cartridge more viable with it's longer barrel and 9 round tube.</entitydescription.sgt_levergun>
  <entityname.sgt_heavyblaster>Heavy Blaster</entityname.sgt_heavyblaster>
  <entitydescription.sgt_heavyblaster>An attempt at generalized Man-Portable Laser Weaponry, the clunky "Rifle" needs single-shot disposable cells to fire, due to it's output load required to discharge.</entitydescription.sgt_heavyblaster>
  <entityname.sgt_asmd>Blaster Rifle</entityname.sgt_asmd>
  <entitydescription.sgt_asmd>A more mobile, but unforgiving variant of the Heavy Blaster, allowing a shot to ring instantaniously, but requiring a timely recharge afterwards. Useful for "Fragging" groups of tightly-packed targets.</entitydescription.sgt_asmd>
  <entityname.sgt_bolter>Prototype Oppressor Battle Carbine</entityname.sgt_bolter>
  <entitydescription.sgt_bolter>A short rifle that runs on 12.7x55 by means of magazines. It adapts upon the Coalition's favored Oppressor Battle Rifle, built into a smaller package while increasing efficiency of gas usage, allowing it to top-out at a higher rate of fire. This also causes it to jump violently, oftentimes injuring untrained users.</entitydescription.sgt_bolter>
  <entityname.sgt_ppr>Prototype Precision Rifle</entityname.sgt_ppr>
  <entitydescription.sgt_ppr>A semi-automatic 8.6x70mm rifle that neatly fits the Designated Marksman role, it has the ability to force through the majority of helmets and vests, while being quick enough for follow-up shots, in the case that one isn't enough.</entitydescription.sgt_ppr>
  <entityname.sgt_chemthrower>Heavy Chemthrower</entityname.sgt_chemthrower>
  <entitydescription.sgt_chemthrower>A large, bulky flamethrower designed by the Coalition to incinerate the most hardy of flora and fauna alike, the specialised chemical fuel reaching up to over 900 degrees and having significantly better range. However it's bulk makes it extremely difficult for a poorly trained user to operate.</entitydescription.sgt_chemthrower>
  <entityname.heavyshotshell>8-Gauge Shotgun Shell</entityname.heavyshotshell>
  <entitydescription.heavyshotshell>Packed with 12 Steel pellets, the shell has a tendancy to take off doors and limbs alike. It does a better job punching through lighter armor than it's lesser counterpart, though can still make a mess of heavier plate.</entitydescription.heavyshotshell>
  <entityname.heavyhotshell>8-Gauge Incendiary Shell</entityname.heavyhotshell>
  <entitydescription.heavyhotshell>Stocked with magnesium shreds, it spreads violently with a hot mess of sparks, usually leaving targets heavily charred.</entitydescription.heavyhotshell>
  <entityname.heavystunshell>8-Gauge Riot Shotgun Shell</entityname.heavystunshell>
  <entitydescription.heavystunshell>Seated with 4 rubber balls, other non-lethal options are suggested for unskilled users, with heavy recoil still being present.</entitydescription.heavystunshell>
  <entityname.heavysliceshell>8-Gauge "Shredder" Slug Shotgun Shell</entityname.heavysliceshell>
  <entitydescription.heavysliceshell>Contains a Titanium fragmenting slug that causes immense bleeding on target, even through heavy armor.</entitydescription.heavysliceshell>
  <entityname.glshotshell>40mm Grenade Shotshell</entityname.glshotshell>
  <entitydescription.glshotshell>Using 24 Steel BB's, the shell's the "short-range" option for explosive specialists to clear paths in-front of them without harming themselves in the process.</entitydescription.glshotshell>
  <entityname.sgt_bosmg>Coalition Suppressed Heavy SMG</entityname.sgt_bosmg>
  <entitydescription.sgt_bosmg>A 11.43x23 SMG with an extreme firerate and integral suppressor, it's favored by Black-Ops Scouts for its quick knock-down and ammo availablity, though it has a nasty habit of running through ammo very quickly, leading to users firing in short, controlled bursts</entitydescription.sgt_bosmg>
  <entityname.sgt_arpistol>Prototype Short-Barreled Rifle</entityname.sgt_arpistol>
  <entitydescription.sgt_arpistol>Chambered in the intermediate 5.56x45, it has native armor piercing and capacity over any other pistol, but at the cost of a larger profile.</entitydescription.sgt_arpistol>
  <entityname.sgt_usp>Combat Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_usp>
  <entitydescription.sgt_usp>A boxy looking 10x25mm handgun, being favoured by most Coalition operators for it's substantially better power and penetration than both 9x19 and 11.43x23 pistols. Such power however comes at the cost of a heavy pistol and significant recoil impulses that most shooters can't handle.</entitydescription.sgt_usp>
  <entityname.sgt_mk23>Covert Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_mk23>
  <entitydescription.sgt_mk23>A 10x25mm combat pistol, with integrated light and suppressor for use by Coalition Black-Ops. Needing something maneuverable, but hardy to keep as backup, the employment of more expensive alloys helps to lighten the overall weapon without compromising reliability.</entitydescription.sgt_mk23>
  <entityname.sgt_n99>The Wanderer</entityname.sgt_n99>
  <entitydescription.sgt_n99>This 10x25mm pistol has seen some better days, with dents and scratches from every discernable source, but just as reliable as ever. Recoil is extremely manageable, so don't worry about a Kick in the Head.</entitydescription.sgt_n99>
  <entityname.sgt_auto10>Prototype Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_auto10>
  <entitydescription.sgt_auto10>An unorthodox 10x25mm design, with ported barrel and weight distribution for ease of handling during firing. It fires in 2-round bursts to maximize rounds on target, with it doing nothing more but a gentle bounce during its' function.</entitydescription.sgt_auto10>
  <entityname.sgt_apc>Rapid Assault SMG</entityname.sgt_apc>
  <entitydescription.sgt_apc>Loaded in 10x25mm, the weapon is often favored by boarding parties and ship defense crews for the quick output of damage, while the chunky design and stock mitigate the recoil considerably. The magwell accepts both extended and standard magazine types.</entitydescription.sgt_apc>
  <entityname.sgt_hpp>Civilian Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_hpp>
  <entitydescription.sgt_hpp>Designed to fire 10x25mm, the "Plastic Pistol" has lead weights in its' slide to cycle properly, giving it a weighty feel, though doing nothing for the recoil.</entitydescription.sgt_hpp>
  <entityname.sgt_hpc>Semi-Auto Assault SMG</entityname.sgt_hpc>
  <entitydescription.sgt_hpc>Firing 10x25mm, it took the design for the Assault Pistol, added a stock, and extended the barrel, allowing for more accurate fire from less skilled individuals.</entitydescription.sgt_hpc>
  <entityname.sgt_pasmg>Prototype Assault SMG</entityname.sgt_pasmg>
  <entitydescription.sgt_pasmg>A brisk-paced 10x25mm submachine gun with a specialty design, it sacrifices speed for accuracy, leaving the user open to close combat during operations. Though, it seems the 8-Gauge underbarrel was the solution to save this Alien of a weapon.</entitydescription.sgt_pasmg>
  <entityname.sgt_m79>Sawed-Off Grenade Launcher</entityname.sgt_m79>
  <entitydescription.sgt_m79>A short-and-simple 40mm grenade launcher, used by boarding crews to displace crowds and devastate rooms before lead starts flying. Made for use by one hand.</entitydescription.sgt_m79>
  <entityname.sgt_napalm>Chemfuel Canister</entityname.sgt_napalm>
  <entitydescription.sgt_napalm>A high density flammable fuel mixture, designed specifically for the Chemthrower to start an inferno.</entitydescription.sgt_napalm>
  <entityname.sgt_hbcell>Heavy Blaster Cell</entityname.sgt_hbcell>
  <entitydescription.sgt_hbcell>Disposable High-Amp Supercapacitor designed for the Heavy Blaster. Better made cells can get more shots before the entropy destroys it.</entitydescription.sgt_hbcell>
  <entityname.sgt_hbcell2>Heavy Blaster Multi-Pulse Cell</entityname.sgt_hbcell2>
  <entitydescription.sgt_hbcell2>Disposable High-Amp Supercapacitor designed for the Heavy Blaster. Having the diodes aligned in series instead of parallel lets the pulse divide, while also increasing the max overall damage due to less strain on the lenses.</entitydescription.sgt_hbcell2>
  <entityname.sgt_10mmmag>Assault Pistol Magazine</entityname.sgt_10mmmag>
  <entitydescription.sgt_10mmmag>Holding 10 rounds of 10x25mm, the cartidge has a few fans due to native AP abilities, but the wrist-wrecking recoil will deter some users.</entitydescription.sgt_10mmmag>
  <entityname.sgt_10mmmagext>Assault Pistol Extended Magazine</entityname.sgt_10mmmagext>
  <entitydescription.sgt_10mmmagext>Holding 20 rounds of 10x25mm, some weapons cannot use this magazine due to it's bulky nature, though the separatists accounted for this in their designs.</entitydescription.sgt_10mmmagext>
  <entityname.sgt_s63>Combat Light Machine Gun</entityname.sgt_s63>
  <entitydescription.sgt_s63>Another work-around to use Coalition ammunition stores, this 5.56x45 LMG can take both Coalition standard rifle magazines and belt boxes. It's assembly is crude at best, so don't expect much from it.</entitydescription.sgt_s63>
  <entityname.sgt_medgas>Sedative Gas Grenade</entityname.sgt_medgas>
  <entitydescription.sgt_medgas>A deployable canister of Chloral Hydrate, used to knock out P.O.I. without injury and allow easier apprehension. The dispersion is quick, but inefficient.</entitydescription.sgt_medgas>
  <entityname.sgt_ext>Pocket Fire Extinguisher</entityname.sgt_ext>
  <entitydescription.sgt_ext>A single-use mini extinguisher, meant to put out fires before they have a chance to take-off.</entitydescription.sgt_ext>
  <entityname.sgt_toolbox>Toolkit</entityname.sgt_toolbox>
  <entitydescription.sgt_toolbox>A toolbox containing everything needed for repairs and fieldwork, with a few open pockets for stowing additional supplies. It's made of Iron. It's very Robust.</entitydescription.sgt_toolbox>
  <entityname.sgt_wrench>Utility Wrench</entityname.sgt_wrench>
  <entitydescription.sgt_wrench>A stronger and more balanced durasteel wrench.</entitydescription.sgt_wrench>
  <entityname.sgt_henrytac>Prototype Repeater</entityname.sgt_henrytac>
  <entitydescription.sgt_henrytac>A heavily updated, multi-calibre Repeater capable of chambering 9x29, 9x33 and 10.9x33, making it significantly more versatile at the cost of a complicated lever and bolt system that needs some decent skill to cycle correctly.</entitydescription.sgt_henrytac>
  <entityname.sgt_crowbar>Durasteel Crowbar</entityname.sgt_crowbar>
  <entitydescription.sgt_crowbar>A weighty and durable wrecking bar made from durasteel. Sometimes it has to be a crowbar coming at them down a steel corridor.</entitydescription.sgt_crowbar>
  <entityname.sgt_syringeshotgun>Syringe Shotgun</entityname.sgt_syringeshotgun>
  <entitydescription.sgt_syringeshotgun>A design questionable by most, it discharges all of it's held syringes in a moments notice. Good for injecting concoxions or intensifying one toxin. Pressure chambers require all others to discharge before they will refill automatically.</entitydescription.sgt_syringeshotgun>
  <entityname.sgt_rifle>Semi-Auto Rifle</entityname.sgt_rifle>
  <entitydescription.sgt_rifle>A stark comparison to the more reliable bolt-action Coalition counterpart, it has a deeper internal magazine, with a self-actuating bolt. The gas system is incredibly rudimentary, and pulls enough away from the round to cause decreased performance.</entitydescription.sgt_rifle>
  <entityname.sgt_rifleprototype>Prototype Automatic Rifle</entityname.sgt_rifleprototype>
  <entitydescription.sgt_rifleprototype>A more dated design, with some odd touches, it uses a hinged magazine with intent to be fed .30 caliber rounds individually. It's barrel assembly was never truly finished, as it's rifling causes some rounds to yaw in-air, losing penetrative power in the process.</entitydescription.sgt_rifleprototype>
  <!--Surplus-->
  <entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>Engineering Overalls</entityname.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>
  <entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>A set of clothing with all the bells and whistles for the tradesman, including a few pockets to store the tools or snacks. Though the inlaid padding helps with the comfort and protection of the wearer, it does hinder movement a little.</entitydescription.scp_heavymechanicsuit1>
  <entityname.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>Engineering Overalls (Style 2)</entityname.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>
  <entitydescription.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>A set of clothing with all the bells and whistles for the tradesman, including a few pockets to store the tools or snacks. Though the inlaid padding helps with the comfort and protection of the wearer, it does hinder movement a little. Maybe blue isn't your color.</entitydescription.sgt_heavymechanicsuit>
  <entityname.scp_t5000>Military Precision Rifle</entityname.scp_t5000>
  <entitydescription.scp_t5000>A large 8.6x70mm rifle designed for quickly and precisely taking out a single person, it is a rare sight on Europa given it's long range nich is very situational.</entitydescription.scp_t5000>
  <entityname.scp_t5000boxmag>Precision Rifle Magazine</entityname.scp_t5000boxmag>
  <entitydescription.scp_t5000boxmag>A small 5 round 8.6x70mm box magazine containing FMJ ammunition.</entitydescription.scp_t5000boxmag>
  <entityname.scp_86projectile>8.6x70mm round</entityname.scp_86projectile>
  <entityname.scp_m24>Revised Precision Rifle</entityname.scp_m24>
  <entitydescription.scp_m24>An 8.6x70mm rifle made to be an alternative to the Coalition's more fine-crafted Precision Rifle. The cartridge's recoil is intense as it clearly was a design that wasn't meant to use it.</entitydescription.scp_m24>
  <entitydescription.scp_86projectile></entitydescription.scp_86projectile>
  <!--Missions-->
  <missionname.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>High-Profile Renegade Bounty</missionname.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>
  <missiondescription.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>There's a small group of "Hyper-Lethal" targets at [location1] that have a high price on their heads, put on by the Separatist party. If blood flows, the Coalition wouldn't be too happy.</missiondescription.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>
  <missionsuccess.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>The Operatives have been successfully neutralized.</missionsuccess.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>
  <missionfailure.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>The squad is left alive.</missionfailure.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>
  <missionheader0.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>Kill Squad Eliminated</missionheader0.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>
  <missionmessage0.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>The Black-Ops Operatives inside have been dealt with, undock to leave the outpost.</missionmessage0.abandonedoutpostassassinatebo>
  <!--Admin-->
  <entityname.sgt_adminskillbook>Specialist Training Handbook</entityname.sgt_adminskillbook>
  <entitydescription.sgt_adminskillbook>A booklet containing uncensored details about some Black-Ops under the ice, and how they were performed, to the letter. Reading this feels like you've walked the steps in their boots. 
    
  This is an Admin item.</entitydescription.sgt_adminskillbook>
  <entityname.sgt_adminmechbook>Exosuit Maintenance Manual</entityname.sgt_adminmechbook>
  <entitydescription.sgt_adminmechbook>A boring step-by-step process to maintain an Exosuit, and some neat tricks to use it better. Atleast it has plenty of pictures.

  This is an Admin item.</entitydescription.sgt_adminmechbook>
  <entityname.sgt_admingenbook>Sailors Guide, Abridged and Refined</entityname.sgt_admingenbook>
  <entitydescription.sgt_admingenbook>This covers everything to a more straight-forward degree, from how to replace motor chucks, to swerving around ice spires, and handling a firearm in an effective manner.


  This is an Admin item.</entitydescription.sgt_admingenbook>
  <entityname.adminxpbook>Smoldered Journal</entityname.adminxpbook>
  <entitydescription.adminxpbook>There's a very distinguishable 3-letter name on the front, though this doesn't explain why it has nonsensical phrases and coordnates. What is at North latitude, 28 degrees, 24 minutes, West longitude 80 degrees, 36 minutes? Is it worth some bizzare adventure?


  This is an Admin item.</entitydescription.adminxpbook>
</infotexts>