<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <!--medical_medical-->
  <entityname.scp_smallcivkit>First Aid Kit</entityname.scp_smallcivkit>
  <entitydescription.scp_smallcivkit>A small kit full of common treatments for nonlife-threatening injuries, it is found all across Europa as a result of it's ease of production and is mostly required by Coalition safety standards.</entitydescription.scp_smallcivkit>
  <entityname.scp_largecivkit>Large First Aid Kit</entityname.scp_largecivkit>
  <entitydescription.scp_largecivkit>A large derivative of the smaller first aid kit, containing more supplies for greater injuries or simply dealing with minor injuries in a large crew.</entitydescription.scp_largecivkit>
  <entityname.scp_largearmykit>Large Military First Aid Kit</entityname.scp_largearmykit>
  <entitydescription.scp_largearmykit>A large medical kit designed for use by combat medics out in the field where they will be distant from any sort of intensive care, coming with various tools and chemical compounds to deal with most injuries caused by weapons, however requires a skilled user to utilise properly.</entitydescription.scp_largearmykit>
  <entityname.scp_armykit>Combat First Aid Kit</entityname.scp_armykit>
  <entitydescription.scp_armykit>a medical kit specifically designed for dealing with injuries caused by firearms and blades, as a result it is excellent for stabilising most severe physical injuries.</entitydescription.scp_armykit>
  <entityname.scp_surgicalkit>Combat Surgical Kit</entityname.scp_surgicalkit>
  <entitydescription.scp_surgicalkit>A medical kit containing surgical equipment for dealing with immediately life threatening physical injuries, though requires a dedicated medic to use as such equipment needs extensive training.</entitydescription.scp_surgicalkit>
  <entityname.scp_tourniquet>Combat Tourniquet</entityname.scp_tourniquet>
  <entitydescription.scp_tourniquet>A device meant to effectively stop even the most severe of bleeding, making it useful in immediately life threatening cases, however using it incorrectly can cause significant damage.</entitydescription.scp_tourniquet>
  <entityname.scp_healthpills>Rejuvination Pills</entityname.scp_healthpills>
  <entitydescription.scp_healthpills>a plastic bottle containing capsuled pills with a highly experimental powdered mutagenic chemical, remaining in the body for a long period of time and treating most physical and biological abnormalities. Caution must be taken however due to the sheer stress this imparts on the patient's vital structures.</entitydescription.scp_healthpills>
  <entityname.scp_painkillers>Painkillers</entityname.scp_painkillers>
  <entitydescription.scp_painkillers>a plastic bottle containing capsuled pills of powdered opiates, remediating minor pain caused by phyiscal trauma and is an excellent option in conjunction with bed rest.</entitydescription.scp_painkillers>
  <entityname.scp_firelatexhot>Refined Ignis Latex Syringe</entityname.scp_firelatexhot>
  <entitydescription.scp_firelatexhot>A sample of Ignis Latex which has been modified to further enhance it's exothermic reaction, causing severe burns within seconds after contact with skin.</entitydescription.scp_firelatexhot>
  <entityname.scp_replicatinglatexrefined>Diluted Preso Latex Syringe</entityname.scp_replicatinglatexrefined>
  <entitydescription.scp_replicatinglatexrefined>A sample of Preso Latex which has been chemically modified to take advantage of Preso latex's mutagenic properties, directly counteracting any Preso Latex reactions alongside partially inverting celluar atrophy caused by Ionizing Radiation.</entitydescription.scp_replicatinglatexrefined>
  <entityname.scp_diamorphine>Diamorphine</entityname.scp_diamorphine>
  <entitydescription.scp_diamorphine>An incredibly potent opiate with immensely high addictivity and potential danger. It can be used to treat the most excruciating pain and to a degree flush out chemicals and infections.</entitydescription.scp_diamorphine>
  <entityname.scp_concoction>The Concoction</entityname.scp_concoction>
  <entitydescription.scp_concoction>A syringe containing a mixture of Morbusine, Radiotoxin and Sufforin, capable of inflicting a horrendous death upon an individual you are especially not fond of in addition to being difficult to remediate. This practice of combining toxins is outlawed due to the intense degree of suffering it causes to an individual.</entitydescription.scp_concoction>
  <entityname.scp_vodka>Condensed Ethanol</entityname.scp_vodka>
  <entitydescription.scp_vodka>A bottle of high quality ethanol that should be used in small doses as a result of its potency. It is capable of flushing out free-radicals and poisons from the circulatory system as veins and arteries vasolidate.</entitydescription.scp_vodka>
  <entityname.scp_pomegrenadedrink>Pomegrenade Punch</entityname.scp_pomegrenadedrink>
  <entitydescription.scp_pomegrenadedrink>A bottle of Pomegrenade juice and Condensed Ethanol, providing an excellent drink for thirsty submariners who want a quick break from something.</entitydescription.scp_pomegrenadedrink>
  <entityname.scp_propital>Combat Stimulant Autoinjector</entityname.scp_propital>
  <entitydescription.scp_propital>An autoinjector using long lasting Anabolic Steroids and analgesics to boost both tissue regeneration and blood coagulation, making it an excellent choice for imminent combat scenarios.</entitydescription.scp_propital>
  <entityname.scp_condensedstabilozine>Condensed Stabilozine Autoinjector</entityname.scp_condensedstabilozine>
  <entitydescription.scp_condensedstabilozine>An autoinjector containing Anabolic Steroids and high levels of Stabilozine for use against most poisons and minor radiation exposure. It features a multi-stage injection system allowing for multiple small doses, though is liable to fail due to being fairly experimental.</entitydescription.scp_condensedstabilozine>
  <entityname.scp_adrenaline>Adrenaline Autoinjector</entityname.scp_adrenaline>
  <entitydescription.scp_adrenaline>An autoinjector comprised of Adrenaline, which is useful for reviving unconscious patients from oxygen deprivation and marginally increasing combat capabilities.</entitydescription.scp_adrenaline>
  <entityname.scp_themedicbag>The Medic Bag.</entityname.scp_themedicbag>
  <entitydescription.scp_themedicbag>AAAAAAAH!</entitydescription.scp_themedicbag>
  <entityname.scp_panacea>Panacea</entityname.scp_panacea>
  <entitydescription.scp_panacea>A mysterious and near perfect looking capsule that is impossible to open regardless of technique. The chemical inside through an unknown and non-replicable process directly reads from the consumer's genetic information and causes a body-wide 'reset' to abnormal and normal cellular structures, freeing the consumer from any injuries. This works especially well against foreign pathogens such as Prionic, Viral and Bacterial infections.</entitydescription.scp_panacea>
  <entityname.scp_devilsblood>Devil's Blood Syringe</entityname.scp_devilsblood>
  <entitydescription.scp_devilsblood>A syringe of processed Sulphuric Acid and Ignis Latex that actively liquefies organic tissues and causes massive internal haemorrhaging. This process as expected is excruciatingly painful and traumatic for the victim.</entitydescription.scp_devilsblood>
  <entityname.scp_wastingdiseasesyringe>Submariner's Wasting Disease Syringe</entityname.scp_wastingdiseasesyringe>
  <entitydescription.scp_wastingdiseasesyringe>A syringe containing a poorly understood neurodegenerative prion disease commonly found dormant within various Europan creatures. These prions are activated through stimulating alien blood with the highly mutagenic Preso Latex and Sufforin, allowing for the proteins to misfold and become malignant.</entitydescription.scp_wastingdiseasesyringe>
  <entityname.scp_wastingdiseasecure>Wasting Disease Antidote</entityname.scp_wastingdiseasecure>
  <entitydescription.scp_wastingdiseasecure>A syringe predominantly containing Stabilozine, capable of neutralising the malignant protein structures responsible for SWD.</entitydescription.scp_wastingdiseasecure>
  <entityname.scp_lineavirussyringe>Brunhes Lineavirus Syringe</entityname.scp_lineavirussyringe>
  <entitydescription.scp_lineavirussyringe>A syringe containing an extremely contagious specimen of an airborne and waterborne virus that has been identified since humanity arrived, primarily affecting the respiratory and gastrointestinal system. Using Sufforin and Preso Latex as a potent activating agent, this specimen is ready for use in biological warfare. CBRN protection will be mandatory once this begins to spread.</entitydescription.scp_lineavirussyringe>
  <entityname.scp_lineaviruscure>Brunhes Lineavirus Antidote</entityname.scp_lineaviruscure>
  <entitydescription.scp_lineaviruscure>A syringe predominantly containing Stabilozine and ABX, capable of dissolving the protein coating of the lineavirus virions and allowing fast recovery in addition to temporary immunity.</entitydescription.scp_lineaviruscure>
  <entityname.scp_volatilereplicatinglatex>Volatile Preso Latex Canister</entityname.scp_volatilereplicatinglatex>
  <entitydescription.scp_volatilereplicatinglatex>A highly unstable form of Preso Latex that readily and spotaneously attempts to react with any organic tissue within close proximity of itself. Holding onto this for a long period of time is highly discouraged.</entitydescription.scp_volatilereplicatinglatex>
  <entityname.scp_psyblock>Antipsychotic Pills</entityname.scp_psyblock>
  <entitydescription.scp_psyblock>A set of pills designed to protect against various mental ailments and the mysterious electromagnetic radiation emitting from Alien Ruins.</entitydescription.scp_psyblock>
  <entityname.ethertank>Ether Tank</entityname.ethertank>
  <entitydescription.ethertank>Portable anesthetic container.</entitydescription.ethertank>
  <entityname.suture>Suture Kit</entityname.suture>
  <entitydescription.suture>Stitches up surgical incisions.</entitydescription.suture>
  <entityname.scalpel>Scalpel</entityname.scalpel>
  <entitydescription.scalpel>Can make very precise cuts, perfect for surgery.</entitydescription.scalpel>
  <entityname.tweezers>Tweezers</entityname.tweezers>
  <entitydescription.tweezers>Allows the retrieval of objects through incisions.</entitydescription.tweezers>
  <entityname.meddegree>Medical Degree</entityname.meddegree>
  <entitydescription.meddegree>A reminder of the good times you had before your medical license was revoked.</entitydescription.meddegree>
  <entityname.surgeryscissors>Surgical Scissors</entityname.surgeryscissors>
  <entitydescription.surgeryscissors>Can make very precise snips, perfect for surgery.</entitydescription.surgeryscissors>
  <entityname.humanorgan>Human Organ</entityname.humanorgan>
  <entitydescription.humanorgan>An organ, of a human.</entitydescription.humanorgan>
  <entityname.humanflesh>Human Flesh</entityname.humanflesh>
  <entitydescription.humanflesh>A flesh sample of the human species.</entitydescription.humanflesh>
  <entityname.surgeryimplant>Surgery Implant</entityname.surgeryimplant>
  <entitydescription.surgeryimplant>An implant that triggers the production of hormones like adrenaline to aid surgery when not in a medical bed or anesthized.</entitydescription.surgeryimplant>
  <entityname.addictionimplant>Addiction Implant</entityname.addictionimplant>
  <entitydescription.addictionimplant>A one-use implant that reprograms the brain to lose its dependence on any drugs.</entitydescription.addictionimplant>
  <entityname.omnizine>Omnizine</entityname.omnizine>
  <entitydescription.omnizine>A medicine capable of healing multiple internal injuries and burns at once.</entitydescription.omnizine>
  <entityname.calomel>Calomel</entityname.calomel>
  <entitydescription.calomel>An aggressive purging agent designed to rid of poisons in early stages.</entitydescription.calomel>
  <entityname.heparin>Heparin</entityname.heparin>
  <entitydescription.heparin>An anti-coagulant for dealing with blood clots.</entitydescription.heparin>
  <entityname.proconvertin>Proconvertin</entityname.proconvertin>
  <entitydescription.proconvertin>An coagulant that helps heal bleeding wounds faster.</entitydescription.proconvertin>
  <entityname.stypticpowder>Styptic Powder</entityname.stypticpowder>
  <entitydescription.stypticpowder>A powder designed to heal brute force and deep tissure injuries.</entitydescription.stypticpowder>
  <entityname.concentratedants>Concentrated Ants</entityname.concentratedants>
  <entitydescription.concentratedants>A bunch of ants in a syringe; often used as a torture method.</entitydescription.concentratedants>
  <entityname.anticide>Anticide</entityname.anticide>
  <entitydescription.anticide>A pesticide designed specifically for ants.</entitydescription.anticide>
  <entityname.symbiotichuskeggs>Lexaneps Calyx Eggs</entityname.symbiotichuskeggs>
  <entitydescription.symbiotichuskeggs>A special compound of velanaceps calyx eggs and special chemicals developed for advanced husk communion repressing the husk infection's ability to fully take over the body. Provides the pros and cons of being a husk without losing sentience.</entitydescription.symbiotichuskeggs>
  <entityname.foldingsurgerytable>Folding Surgical Table</entityname.foldingsurgerytable>
  <entitydescription.foldingsurgerytable>A folding surgical table used in the event of missing a hospital bed.</entitydescription.foldingsurgerytable>
  <itemmsglaydownselect>[[select]] Lay down</itemmsglaydownselect>
  <itemmsgfoldtableselect>[[use]] Fold up</itemmsgfoldtableselect>
  <entityname.basebionic>Bionic Organ</entityname.basebionic>
  <entitydescription.basebionic>A bionic contraption to mimic the function of a normal human organ, can be used to replace missing organs. Mostly used to create complex bionic organs with new functions to offer to the body.</entitydescription.basebionic>
  <entityname.adrenalinebionic>Bionic Adrenaline Gland</entityname.adrenalinebionic>
  <entitydescription.adrenalinebionic>A bionic organ designed to produce advanced and alien variations of natural hormones to increase body performance.</entitydescription.adrenalinebionic>
  <entityname.methbionic>Bionic Hyperactive Gland</entityname.methbionic>
  <entitydescription.methbionic>An experimental bionic organ designed to produce stimulants like methamphetamine. Do not ingest alcohol while in body.</entitydescription.methbionic>
  <entityname.gillsbionic>Bionic Gills</entityname.gillsbionic>
  <entitydescription.gillsbionic>A bionic organ designed to allow the supply of oxygen underwater. Does not protect against pressure.</entitydescription.gillsbionic>
  <entityname.mechanitebionic>Bionic Mechanite Gland</entityname.mechanitebionic>
  <entitydescription.mechanitebionic>A bionic organ designed to produce nanomachines (called mechanites) that support and strengthen the empidermis to protect from barotrauma.</entitydescription.mechanitebionic>
  <entityname.calyxanidebionic>Bionic Calyxanide Gland</entityname.calyxanidebionic>
  <entitydescription.calyxanidebionic>An experimental bionic organ designed to produce calyxanide in the system, sort of like a husk vaccine. Shunned by the church of the husk.</entitydescription.calyxanidebionic>
  <entityname.bloodbionic>Bionic Blood Transmutator</entityname.bloodbionic>
  <entitydescription.bloodbionic>A bionic organ designed to transmutate any alien or foreign blood efficiently into usable human blood.</entitydescription.bloodbionic>
  <entityname.sleepypen>Sleepy Pen</entityname.sleepypen>
  <entitydescription.sleepypen>A auto syringe injector with the design of a regular pen, does not make any noise like any other syringe; all chemicals injected with this special syringe have their effects delayed as well.</entitydescription.sleepypen>
  <entityname.autosurgeon>Autosurgeon</entityname.autosurgeon>
  <entitydescription.autosurgeon>An automated device that complete surgeries very quickly. Not exactly efficient, using it's entire internal battery content for a single use; suggested only to be used in an emergency event. Recharges when a battery is placed inside it.</entitydescription.autosurgeon>
  <entityname.surgeonprogrambullet>Autosurgeon Program: Bullet Removal</entityname.surgeonprogrambullet>
  <entitydescription.surgeonprogrambullet>Datachip containing autosurgeon instructions for the removal of a bullet lodged in the body.</entitydescription.surgeonprogrambullet>
  <entityname.surgeonprogramorgan>Autosurgeon Program: Organ Removal</entityname.surgeonprogramorgan>
  <entitydescription.surgeonprogramorgan>Datachip containing autosurgeon instructions for the removal of a organ, primarily for transplant reasons.</entitydescription.surgeonprogramorgan>
  <jobname.medicaldoctor3>Surgeon</jobname.medicaldoctor3>
  <jobdescription.medicaldoctor3>These specialists are prepared to quickly and effectively perform surgery in a submarine ship for extended amounts of time.</jobdescription.medicaldoctor3>
  <entityname.doctorsuniform3>Surgeon's Uniform</entityname.doctorsuniform3>
  <entitydescription.doctorsuniform3>Makes you look like you might be useful if your forged medical degree didn't already show that.</entitydescription.doctorsuniform3>
  <entitydescription.antidama1>A powerful opiate for treating pain and stabilizing critical patients, but will cause shortness of breath and eventual dependency with overuse.</entitydescription.antidama1>
  <entitydescription.antidama2>A powerful opiate for treating pain and stabilizing critical patients, but will cause shortness of breath and eventual dependency with overuse.</entitydescription.antidama2>
  <entitydescription.tonicliquid>A medical solution that's commonly used as an ingredient in more complex medical compounds.</entitydescription.tonicliquid>
  <entitydescription.antinarc>An emergency use opioid antagonist for the treatment of overdose.</entitydescription.antinarc>
  <entitydescription.stabilozine>Used as an ingredient in the manufacture of various medicines. On its own, can be used to slow down the effects of most toxins. Also good for treating organ rejection.</entitydescription.stabilozine>

</infotexts>