<Override>
  <infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
    <jobname.assistant>Specialist</jobname.assistant>
    <!--weapons_overrides-->
    <entityname.smg>Surplus Submachine Gun</entityname.smg>
    <entitydescription.smg>An old, surplus 11.43x23mm SMG based on an Israeli design that has been on Europa since humanity arrived. Its large sealed bolt severely hampers its cyclic rate and as a result it has been mostly phased out by other options, as more sophisticated bolt designs were made allowing for more reliable options to be developed.</entitydescription.smg>
    <entityname.smgmagazine>Surplus Submachine Gun Magazine</entityname.smgmagazine>
    <entitydescription.smgmagazine>A surplus, old and semi-cumbersome 25 round 11.43x23mm magazine intended for use in the older Coalition SMGs, its shape designed for the cartridges that contain an older form of oxidizing propellant.</entitydescription.smgmagazine>
    <entityname.smground></entityname.smground>
    <entitydescription.smground></entitydescription.smground>
    <entityname.revolver>Surplus Defensive Revolver</entityname.revolver>
    <entitydescription.revolver>A 9x29mm revolver utilizing an old military service cartridge for use in revolvers, all the way to the Vietnam war almost over 400 years ago. It has a very light double action trigger mechanism.</entitydescription.revolver>
    <entityname.revolverround>Surplus Defensive Revolver Round</entityname.revolverround>
    <entitydescription.revolverround>An old 9x29mm cartridge that appears to no longer be produced on Europa anymore, despite this it is incredibly common due to the collosal Surplus though has sub-par stopping power compared to modern options.</entitydescription.revolverround>
    <entityname.shotgun>Surplus Riot Shotgun</entityname.shotgun>
    <entitydescription.shotgun>A very worn, cheap and used looking 12 gauge pump action shotgun with a very stiff pump action based on an Italian design, originally intended for engaging unarmoured targets and general security onboard a submarine or within an outpost. It has been mostly phased out by the more modern Pump Action Shotgun options.</entitydescription.shotgun>
    <entityname.shotgunshell>12 Gauge Shotgun Buckshot Shell</entityname.shotgunshell>
    <entitydescription.shotgunshell>An extremely common and popular 12 gauge shotgun shell containing buckshot that's found practically all across Europa, renowned for it's close quarters lethality despite it's non-existent armour penetration.</entitydescription.shotgunshell>
    <entityname.ancientweapon>Alien Gamma Ray Tool</entityname.ancientweapon>
    <entitydescription.ancientweapon>A strange, organic looking device made out of various heavy metals and Fulgurium, capable of releasing high energy, concentrated gamma emissions to disrupt solid matter.</entitydescription.ancientweapon>
    <entityname.harpoongun>Harpoon Launcher</entityname.harpoongun>
    <entitydescription.harpoongun>A basic weapon intended for use underwater against creatures such as crawlers and small fish, but not intended for infantry combat, but can be put into such a role if your situation is especially desperate.</entitydescription.harpoongun>
    <entityname.smgunique>Aftermarket Surplus SMG</entityname.smgunique>
    <entitydescription.smgunique>A surplus SMG which has been modified to fill a carbine role, having a significantly higher cyclic rate from the gas block being located closer to the start of the barrel and is a lot more accurate, as a result of precision rifling inside of the barrel.</entitydescription.smgunique>
    <entityname.shotgununique>Veteran's Double Barrel Shotgun</entityname.shotgununique>
    <entitydescription.shotgununique>A very old shotgun with 2 side-by-side barrels and 2 linked triggers, allowing for 2 shells to be discharged almost immediately. Unfortunately due to being a double barreled shotgun its capacity is inferior to practically every other design.</entitydescription.shotgununique>
    <entityname.handcannon>Veteran's Hand Cannon</entityname.handcannon>
    <entitydescription.handcannon>A massive 15.5x50mm revolver which uses a ridiculously large cartridge that resembles a small grenade shell. It has a very heavy double action trigger mechanism.</entitydescription.handcannon>
    <entityname.handcannonround>Veteran's Hand Cannon Round</entityname.handcannonround>
    <entitydescription.handcannonround>A massive 15.5x50mm cartridge with a Titanium-Alloy jacketed Physicorium tip, capable of penetrating multiple enemies and is guarranteed to immediately disable every one of them.</entitydescription.handcannonround>
    <entityname.assaultrifle>Surplus Assault Rifle</entityname.assaultrifle>
    <entitydescription.assaultrifle>A 6.8x51mm assault rifle used in the early years of Coalition proliferation though has mostly been succeeded by the more refined designs. The schematics can be rarely found as a result.</entitydescription.assaultrifle>
    <entityname.assaultriflemagazine>Surplus Assault Rifle Magazine</entityname.assaultriflemagazine>
    <entitydescription.assaultriflemagazine>A 20 steel round 6.8x51mm magazine containing an old form of experimental ammunition, composed mostly of a steel jacket with a Physicorium core, providing excellent armour defeating capabilities. This ammo has however been discontinued given it's cost.</entitydescription.assaultriflemagazine>
    <entityname.assaultrifleround>assaultrifleround</entityname.assaultrifleround>
    <entitydescription.assaultrifleround></entitydescription.assaultrifleround>
    <entityname.autoshotgun>Surplus Automatic Shotgun</entityname.autoshotgun>
    <entitydescription.autoshotgun>A very early design for an automatic 12 gauge shotgun, created during the time Europan settlers had few weaponry.</entitydescription.autoshotgun>
    <entityname.stungundart>Stun Gun Dart</entityname.stungundart>
    <entitydescription.stungundart>A small electronic dart designed to inflict multiple short burst electric currents over a period of time into the person it sticks into, causing involuntary muscle movement and temporary paralysis.</entitydescription.stungundart>
    <entityname.spear>Harpoon</entityname.spear>
    <entitydescription.spear>A simple rod of steel with a sharp, barbed point on the end for use against fish and your own crew.</entitydescription.spear>
    <entityname.magnesium>Magnesium</entityname.magnesium>
    <entitydescription.magnesium>A powdered alkali element that is popular as a propellant on Europa for various low calibre cartridges and some medicines.</entitydescription.magnesium>
    <entityname.lead>Lead</entityname.lead>
    <entitydescription.lead>A dense, malleable element that is very toxic when ingested. Whilst easy to extract and quite common on Europa, supply is low with a very high demand as a result of it's pivotal role in submarine turret and firearm ammunition.</entitydescription.lead>
    <entityname.grenadelauncher>Surplus Grenade Launcher</entityname.grenadelauncher>
    <entitydescription.grenadelauncher>A worn and old 40x46mm grenade launcher used for area denial or attacking multiple targets within a group.</entitydescription.grenadelauncher>
    <entityname.stungrenade>Stun Grenade</entityname.stungrenade>
    <entitydescription.stungrenade>A less-than-lethal grenade meant to disorient aggressive individuals without causing significant harm, creating an intense bang and blinding light.</entitydescription.stungrenade>
    <entityname.shotgunshellblunt>12 Gauge Rubber Shotgun Slug</entityname.shotgunshellblunt>
    <entitydescription.shotgunshellblunt>A 12 gauge slug made completely out of rubber, made for pain compliance and subduing troublemakers without needing other options. However due to its less-lethal nature it is a terrible choice for a person who is armed and an immediate threat to others.</entitydescription.shotgunshellblunt>
  </infotexts>
</Override>